(Raj:)Here's what I wonder
about zombies.
(Raj:)What happens if they can't get
any human flesh to eat?
(Raj:)They can't starve to death--
they're already dead.
(Howard:)You take this one.
I spent an hour last night on
"How do vampires shave
(Howard:)when they can't see
themselves in the mirror"?
(Sheldon:)Well-groomed vampires
meet in pairs
(Sheldon:)and shave each other--
case closed.
(Raj:)Yeah, okay, so, zombies.
(Leonard:)I guess it depends
on the zombies, Raj.
(Leonard:)Are we talking slow zombies,
fast zombies?
Like, in 28 Days,
if those zombies didn't eat,
(Leonard:)they starved.
You're thinking
of 28 Days Later.
28 Days is where
Sandra Bullock goes to rehab
(Howard:)and puts the audience
into an undead state
(Raj:)Hey, don't bag
on Sandra Bullock!
(Raj:)You think it makes you
look cultured,
(Raj:)but you just
come off as bitter.
(Leonard:)Oh, Dr. Siebert,
twelve o'clock.
(Howard:)Why's the president
of the university
(Howard:)slumming in the cafeteria?
(Sheldon:)Perhaps he's emulating
Shakespeare's Henry V,
(Sheldon:)who dressed as a commoner
and mingled among them,